- Scotty , Scotty .
Where 's my little pal ?
Come on .
Off to bed .
There , there , Scotty .
Now , now , now , now , boy .
It 's all right .
It 's only the storm .
Come on .
Yes .
Here we go .
There 's a boy .
Oh , God !
Scotty !
No !
Where are you ?
Come .
Come back to me !
My little baby !
- This hearing is to determine whether Jake Matthew Cullen
is to be committed for trial for the disappearance and
presumed murder of Scott Matthew Cullen .
- A pig , you say ?
- No , a boar .
Razorback .
- And this , this razorback broke your leg and carried
your grandson away ?
- Yes .
- You mean to say , Mr Cullen , that as a professional
kangaroo shooter armed with a high powered rifle , you were
unable to kill or even wound this boar .
- Your Worship , the animal in question is by no means a
normal product of nature .
It 's armoured in a thick layer of bristle that can 't be
penetrated by a rifle shot unless it 's fired
from underneath it .
- Your Worship , we have already heard expert testimony from
Mr Baker that he shoots and kills razorbacks every day .
- There are all sorts of razorbacks .
It 's a hybrid species .
A freak .
An aberration .
- Aberration or apparition ?
- Quiet !
Quiet !
- Then the answer is no .
You were unable to wound it .
- Well , you 'd have to see it to believe it .
- Indeed .
- Indeed , indeed .
- So , as a professional kangaroo shooter and an expert on
local wildlife , how big would an animal , say , a razorback ,
how large would a razorback have to be to actually carry a
two-year-old child over any distance ?
- About four or five times bigger than anything I 've seen
or heard of .
- For an animal to have grown to such an extraordinay size ,
he must be extremely shy and cunning - -
- Even an exceptionally large and cunning
beast couldn 't have dragged the boy ?
- Where to ?
- Anywhere .
- No , not for any distance .
The razorback 's a kind of cowardly bastard .
Usually a good boo would scare him off .
- Do you often leave the boy with his grandfather ?
- I was away in Brisbane .
My mother was sick .
- Do you know what happened ?
- Objection !
- Overruled .
- Dad said it was a razorback , but what razorback ?
Where is it ?
Why hasn 't anyone else ever seen it ?
- The finding of this court is that there is insufficient
evidence to support the charge .
The accused is hereby discharged .
- Exploitation of animals .
- Exploitation , honey ?
- Carl ?
- Hello .
- Is it on yet , honey ?
- No , it 's still cooking .
It 's nearly ready .
- Oh , you mean the TV ?
- Yeah , it just started .
- They enjoy performing .
- With cattle prods attached to their genitals ?
- We don 't used prods here .
- Oh , God .
- Hey , wait a minute I want to watch that .
- No , please , Carl , leave it off .
- Uh-uh .
Don 't you touch it .
Here .
- No .
- Come on .
Just relax .
- That 's a damn lie .
Not one of our wranglers ever used a prod .
- Would you like to see the proof ?
- Honey , you and your friends wouldn 't know the difference
between a cattle prod and a pool cue .
- Not much different in terms of pain .
- Don 't play with me .
I 've been in the business for twenty years .
- Look at this creep .
- My reputation speaks for itself .
- Unfortunately the animals can 't do the same .
- You start with the horses and steers ,
why don 't you go and save the
fleas and flies and bugs in the world , too ?
They 're animals , aren 't they ?
People swat fleas .
I got no time of day for this .
- Fleas in America .
- Cruelty to rats , too .
- Jerks .
The agency greenlighted the Australia special today .
- On the kangaroo slaughter ?
I thought they passed on that months ago .
- They changed their minds .
And they 're insisting that I go .
- Damn right you should go .
It was your idea in the first place .
Honey , that 's terrific .
Congratulations .
- I 'm scheduled to leave on Monday .
- Oh , well .
- Yeah .
Oh , hon .
- What 's wrong ?
- Oh , I don 't know .
- Come on .
- Prenatal depression .
- What about you ?
- Well , I 'll be utterly and completely miserable ,
but I can probably take care of myself .
- Really ?
- Oh , shit !
Argh !
- Come on .
Here .
Will you miss me ?
- Is the Pope Polish ?
Does a bear shit in the woods ?
- I don 't like being apart on our anniversary .
- You know , there 's a rumour going around that they 've
actually got telephones in Australia now .
I think I even read about it in National Geographic .
- What would they know ?
- Well , I suppose if you 're so determined to run off again
and leave me , I should probably give you your little
surprise now .
- Carl !
It 's beautiful .
- Yeah ?
Good .
Then it suits you .
- Ahem .
- Set .
- We 're 600 miles west of Sydney in the outback town of
Gamulla , an aboriginal word that appropriately means
intestine or gut , appropriate because Gamulla deals
literally in an economy of flesh and blood .
Last year , more than 800,000 kangaroos and waballies .
Wabballies !
- Oh !
Erm .
- Still rolling .
Still rolling .
- From last year , okay ?
Right .
Last year , more than 800,000 kangaroos and wallabies
were slaughtered in this district alone .
They were summarily gutted and quartered and dumped at the
Petpak cannery eight miles west from here , to become dog
excreta on the sidewalks of Sydney , Hong Kong , and New York .
That 'll do .
I 'll do the pampered pet routine in voiceover , okay ?
Well , how did I sound ?
- Wabballies !
Friend of yours ?
G 'day .
We 'd like to book a couple of rooms , please .
- Beth Winters , isn 't it ?
The animal campaigner ?
- Yes , that 's right .
How do we get a message out ?
- Well theres a radio phone , it might take an hour or two to get through .
Where are you ringing ?
- New York .
- New York ?
- You 'll be lucky to get Burke .
- Let 's start with Burke then shall we ?
- Where are the rooms , mate ?
- We , we 'd like to interview some kangaroo shooters .
Anyone interested ?
I see .
Well , I 'll just - -
- Right .
- There 's no way the Petpak cannery 's going to
agree to an interview .
How about we do a walk-in tomorrow ?
- You 're the boss .
All they can do is smash my camera like they did in Dubbo .
- Think positive .
You can collect off my insurance .
- Just remember you 're not in New York , surrounded by
a couple of million animal lovers .
- Let 's get set up .
- Now ?
Now ?
- Hurry !
Sir ?
Sir , my name is Beth Winters and I 'm from the World Animal
League .
How do you respond to claims by Australian Environmental
Scientists that the kangaroo is becoming extinct ?
- Wouldn 't know .
I hunt boars .
- Boars ?
- Razorbacks .
- Well , boars or kangaroos .
You 're a professional hunter , right ?
You make your living by killing wildlife , correct ?
- If you say so .
- Well .
Erm , roughly how many razorbacks would you kill in a season ?
- There isn 't a season for razorbacks , girly .
- Then why kill them ?
- Oh , I don 't know .
There 's something about blasting the shit out of a razorback that brightens up my whole day .
- But surely - -
- Cut .
Come on .
- Hello ?
No .
New York .
United States .
America ?
Erm , sorry .
Over .
Erm , no , I want to telephone there .
I want you to connect me with a landline .
Over .
Winters .
Carl Winters .
He 's the party with whom I wish to speak .
Hello ?
- Mate ?
What do you reckon ?
I reckon .
- Oh sorry sweetheart .
We only want to give you a little freak .
- The roads will be full of kangaroos and sheep after dark .
It wouldn 't look good for the chief of the Animal Lib to be running animals over .
- Thanks for worrying .
I 'll drive slowly and be back by dusk .
Don 't use all the hot water , okay ?
- Who wouldn 't be ?
So they took her to intensive care .
The next day I went to see her and the Mother Superior was there - -
She said , " My dear , how do you feel ? "
The nun says , with her eyes full of tears , " Terrible " .
He hasn 't called , he hasn 't sent any letters .
- What 's up your hole ?
You American shit !
You give me that .
Listen , man , you come round to where we work and you
shoot .
You want this back ?
Quick , Benny !
Benny !
- Bye !
- Oh , yeah .
Bye .
- You idiot !
What 's she doing down there ?
- Come on .
♫ Send me your warning siren
♫ As if I could ever hide
♫ Last time la luna
♫ I light my torch and
♫ Wave it for the
♫ New moon on Monday
♫ And a fire dance
♫ Through the night
- We 're turning left .
- Stop !
Jesus !
- Hi .
Everything okay ?
Any bones broken ?
Anything like that ?
You all right ? You are ok ?
- Yeah .
- Yeah ?
Good .
- I 'll have a go after you , Dicko !
- Mind your own business !
Just relax , just relax !
Don 't rough her up too much , mate !
We don 't want to spoil the goods !
- Go on , son !
That 's right !
- Do you want to make love ? - What ?
I said , I said do you wanna make .
Try it again .
Stay on the bed , Mavis .
That 's a good girl .
- Get her legs up , mate !
- Can 't get her legs open ! - Get her clothes off !
How 's your French .
I said , how 's your French kissing ?
Get into it , doll .
- Hey , cut that out , Dicko !
- Shut your hole !
- You don 't want to kill the bloody woman !
Quick !
Let 's get out of here !
- I 'm just getting her ready !
- Leave her !
Get out of here !
♫ Blue eyes holding back the tears
♫ Holding back the pain
- Going to cost more to tow it back
than the bloody thing 's worth .
Insurance job .
Should have just left it .
Townies run off the road , knock a few posts
down and wander into the bush .
Bloody locals have got to drop
everything and go looking for them .
- He 's back .
- Hey ? You say somethin ?
- I said he 's back .
- Who 's back ?
An old friend .
- Benny !
Benny !
- What do you want , Jake ?
- You were there .
- We were where ?
- You and Dicko .
You saw it .
- What was it we saw ?
- All right .
Where 's Dicko ?
- Dicko didn 't see it .
He didn 't see any boars or any women .
Bye , Jake .
Silly old bugger .
Now get off , you .
- Bye , Jake .
- Cut it out , you mongrel !
Just cut it out !
- Carl , it 's beautiful .
- How do you respond to claims that the kangaroo is becoming extinct ?
- What do you mean , she 's missing ?
- It was an accident .
- My fault .
- How many razorbacks would you kill in a season ?
- There isn 't a season .
- Should never have let her out of my sight .
I don 't know . Something about blasting the shit out of a razorback
that brightens up my day - That 's Jake Cullen .
- Excuse me .
Can you tell me who runs this place ?
- Yeah .
Me .
- Great , I 'd like to reserve a room for the night If I could .
- I 'll give you a bed out the back .
- Where can I find Jake Cullen ?
- Jake ?
Nowadays he 's out about Ten Train Road .
35 miles down this road , turn left at the junction , follow
the road right through to the end .
- How about a taxi or a car for hire ?
- Taxi ?
I haven 't seen a taxi here since about 1953 and he was lost .
Listen , you better take my old bomb .
Just top up the tank when you get back .
- You sure ?
- Sure .
I 'll look after your bag , don 't worry .
- Thanks .
Thanks a lot .
- I 'd watch the steering .
She gets a bit wobbly over the tonne .
- Okay .
Back soon .
- To the left !
- How 's it going ?
- Same as usual .
- Bit dusty , huh ?
- Yeah .
- My name 's Carl Winters .
- Yeah ?
- Jake Cullen , right ?
- What 's it to you ?
- You were one of the last people to see my wife alive .
- Your wife ?
- Beth Winters .
- Oh , yes .
The kangaroo woman .
It 's too bad .
I 'm sorry .
- Thought you might know what happened to her .
- Razorbacks .
Vicious , shit-eating godless vermin .
God and the devil couldn 't have created
a more despicable species .
Here .
See this fella ?
I blew half of his hind quarters away with a 30-30
and he kept coming .
Usually the concussion alone is enough
to knock most animals rotten but .
But your razorback doesn 't have a nervous
system like most animals .
It 's only got two states of being , dangerous or dead .
Nothing in between .
- That 's very interesting .
Now tell me about my wife .
- I sort through their droppings .
You learn a lot from droppings .
- Droppings ?
- Boar shit .
- You 're giving me a lesson in wildlife .
It 's my wife we 're talking about .
The kangaroo woman .
You make it sound as if she has a goddamn pouch .
- Now , listen , son .
You and me , we got something in common .
I know what you 're going through .
- Then help me .
- No proof .
- I 'm not asking for proof .
Just give me some place to start .
- Try the Petpak cannery .
- Hello ?
Hi .
What are you doing ?
- The smell brings the flies in .
I 've got to put these lights up so they don 't clean me out .
American , are you ?
- Ah , no .
Canadian .
- Canadians are American , aren 't they ?
Hop up .
Dicko !
- Hang on !
I 'm busy !
- I got an American out here !
Eh , this is er .
- Bill .
- He 's gonna get a ride out with us to the diggings , mate .
Why don 't you give Dicko a hand until we go ?
- Here .
Take the spade .
Welcome to Petpak .
- You idiot !
I told you to watch it !
What are you trying to do ?
Blow us up ?
Get away !
What do you think you 're doing , Wallace , you idiot !
- I 'll follow you .
- No , you ride with us .
Save yourself a dollar .
- That 's not necessary .
- You can run Turner 's car back tomorrow , can 't you .
Look out for the piggy-wiggies , Wallace !
- Hey , Ten .
- Oh , wipe out !
- You over here on your holidays then ?
- Yeah .
Yeah .
I guess you guys hunt roos in this thing , huh ?
- Yeah .
You do any hunting in Canuck land ?
- Deer .
- Sweetheart .
Get it ?
Dear ?
Hey , hey !
- Yeah , that 's Sarah Cameron 's place .
Hey , you can always pop in for a quick visit .
- Sorry ?
- Yeah , you 'd be sorry all right .
You would be , yeah .
- Homey-poo !
After you !
- Come in .
Watch your step here , Bill .
We 've got plenty of bunks down here .
- Oh no listen , I 've reserved a room in town .
- No , we wouldn 't hear of it .
We like a guest .
In any case , you 're gonna be closer to the diggings here .
And Dicko there 's gonna burn us some snags .
- Snags ?
- You know , bangers .
- Mystery bags .
- What ?
- Sausages .
- Oh , yeah .
I 'm really beat .
If I could use your shower , I 'd like to lay down
for an hour or so .
- Shower ?
You can hose off under the tank if you like .
There you go , Bill .
This is your bunk here , mate .
Nice and soft , eh ?
That 's a good one for you .
You can punch a few Zs away there , mate .
Do you want a rum or anything ?
- I knew you 'd be a fun group as soon as I
saw you with the water beds and whoopee cushions .
You will all give me your names and relatives .
- Wakey , wakey , hands off snakey !
- We 're going hunting , mate .
- Hunting tonight ?
- You don 't shoot roos in the daylight .
They can 't see the spotlight .
There you are .
Don 't be shy .
- Great .
You don 't get many strangers up this way , huh ?
- Nah .
Tourist coach about once a week .
That 's all .
- What about that American woman , Beth Winters ?
- You mean that grunter from New York ?
- What happened to her ?
- Cops say she fell down a mine shaft .
- Friend of yours , was she ?
- Me ?
No .
- You come from over there , don 't you ?
- Never met her , though .
- I-I don 't go along with animal welfare crap .
- How come you came to Petpak ?
How come you came down our place ?
- I was talking to Jake Cullen said you guys knew a lot about opal mining .
- Did he ?
What else did he say ?
- Nothing .
- Oh .
That 's all right , then .
You don 't want to listen to him , mate .
He 's as mad as a meat axe .
- Yep .
You know what ?
He murdered his grandson .
- Is that right ?
- Kid disappeared .
Jake went to court . They tried Jake , but they couldn 't convict him .
They didn 't have enough evidence .
Kid vanished .
It must have been him .
- Maybe he fell down a mine shaft , too .
- You know your trouble ?
You ask too many bloody questions .
You writing a book or something about this Winters woman ?
- Not me .
- You gonna hold onto that all night ?
Get a blanket or something , you know ?
Gets cold enough to freeze the balls off a brass monkey .
Did you ever see them castrating lambs ?
We 'll have to take you out to do that one day .
- You work the spot , Bill , so Dicko can shoot .
Unless we see a mob of big reds .
Then you 'll have to drive so I can shoot too .
Spot 's behind you .
For Christ 's sake , mate , don 't
switch it on until you get up there .
Now just swing it around slow like until you spot one .
And then you hold it there while I cut the donk .
- You cut their donks ?
- The motor .
- No , no !
Left , left , left !
Down !
Up !
That 's it .
Beautiful .
It 's beautiful .
See ?
See how it 's mesmerised with the spot ?
Beautiful big brown eyes .
Fuck me !
- There !
- God .
God !
- What ?
- It 's still alive .
- Of course it is .
You don 't kill it outright .
It 'd go stiff as jerky before you had time to butcher it .
- Strewth !
Charming !
Must have been the snags .
- Sure smells like it .
What 's up , Billy ?
That snag turn in your gut , did it ?
You only had to holler
if you wanted to barf !
- Give me the rifle .
Give me the rifle !
- No way , why do you want it ?
What are you doing ?
Leave it alone !
You killed it !
What did you want to bloody go and do that for ?
You better finish it off now .
Skin it and gut it .
Pretty tough hombre , aren 't you ?
Do you chuck up when
you 're shooting deer ?
That 's mine , see you , Skip .
- You 're in the middle of bugger all here
so for Christ 's sake don 't go walkabout .
We 'll be back in five or six hours .
- Wakey , wakey , hands off snakey !
- Can 't swim .
You can 't swim !
You can 't get me !
Oh !
Oh , God !
No !
No you won 't !
- It 's okay .
It 's okay .
Good morning .
What happened to you out there ?
Car break down ?
- The Baker brothers .
Benny and Dicko took me shooting .
- Yeah , that 'd be their idea of a joke .
- Some boars chased me .
- You were chased by boars ?
- Dozens of them .
I spent the night up a windmill tower .
- At the pumping shed ?
God , they 've busted through the north boundary . They don 't usually come in that close .
- You ever heard of Beth Winters ?
- Animal campaigner ?
Yep .
- She 's my wife .
- She wasn 't very popular around here .
- So I gather .
Do you know what happened to her ?
- She fell down a mine shaft that 's what they say
Lie still , lie down .
Keep still , huh ?
If the boars had you surrounded ,
how the hell did you get away ?
Sorry .
- I don 't know .
Something big scared them away .
- Like what ?
- I don 't know .
But it was huge .
As big as a rhino .
- You just lie still , I 've got to make a call , okay ?
- Sarah tells me you 've seen the boar .
The razorback .
Come on , boy !
- I 'm not sure .
I didn 't see it clearly .
- Tusks around about so .
- I couldn 't say .
It was a long way away .
- I 'm going out there .
- Could it be the same one ?
- It 'll do me .
- Wait , I 'll get the dart gun .
Jake !
If he 's as big as you say you 're not going to
stop him with a 303 .
- I won 't stop him with a dart .
- We can get a transmitter on him at least we can - -
- I don 't want to track him .
I want to nail the bastard 's hide
outside the pub so everyone can see .
- Take the dart gun , please .
Thank you .
- What 's with him ?
Doesn 't he care about anything , but his goddamn razorbacks ?
- A couple of years ago one of them got into his
house and took his grandson .
- It was a razorback ?
- He 's had a private war going ever since .
Took his grandson .
His daughter .
And his pride .
That boar destroyed his life .
- Come on , Spider .
Come on .
We 've got a long wait .
Here , boy .
Here .
Yeah .
- Now in South Australia , instead of
mowing your lawn , you can smoke it .
- Oi !
What are you trying to do ?
Drown the flies ?
- What are you doing ?
- Putting a tag on it .
I keep track of their migration that way .
I got a government grant to carry out research .
It 's more work , but I need the cash .
- So you 're here all alone ?
- Yep .
Jake drops in regularly .
He 's supposed to be my stockman ,
but I can 't get him to take any pay .
- What 's wrong ?
- Oh , nothing , I ...
I 've never seen anyone in Dad 's
trousers since he died , it looks good .
Next time he comes back this way I
catch him and check his growth .
There it is .
- Yeah .
How long have you been all by yourself here ?
- My mum died last year .
Jake 's never more than a radio message away .
- Must be tough .
- It wasn 't so bad a couple of years back .
Now these boars are eating us out of house and home .
- Why has it gotten so bad ?
- We 're not exactly sure .
A lot of them are diseased .
They 've got worms and parasites .
The sicker they get , the hungrier they become .
It 's really weird lately because Jake 's been finding their teeth .
They 've been cannibalising their young .
It 's not normal .
I dissected a sow last week .
Guess what I found .
A stress ulcer .
- Boars worry ?
- Yeah .
Lately something 's been worrying them a lot .
- Jesus wept .
It 's him , Spider .
The big fella .
Sarah was right .
It 's gonna take a lot to stop him .
Go !
Die , you murderous bastard !
Die !
Dart !
They 'll believe me now .
I 'm sorry , son .
The electronic gizmo .
Switch it on .
Gotcha , you murderous bastard .
Where is he ?
- Hang on , Jake , give me a minute .
Looks like he 's about three miles west of the pumping shed .
- There 's no water in 30 miles .
He 's got to come to the water hole to drink .
- If you couldn 't stop him - -
- He 's only bacon .
- Get some help .
- No , he 's mine .
That 458 your father keeps around the place .
That ought to slow him down .
- Be careful , you old goat .
Sorry .
Didn 't agree with her ideas but
I 'm sure she was a good woman .
- Our anniversary .
The day she disappeared was our anniversary .
First one .
She didn 't want to make this trip .
She was six weeks pregnant and worried about the baby .
I 'm the one that convinced her to go .
- Are you okay ?
- Yeah .
- Trying to get in contact with Constable McCleary .
Over .
- He 's been away all week as far as I know .
What 's the trouble , Sarah , over ?
- No trouble , Jake 's camped out at the northeast boundary .
I 'll get him to go over there in the morning .
Over .
- What 's up , over ?
- Jake reckons he knows what happened to the Beth Winters woman .
Over and out .
- I 'll be leaving in the morning .
You 've been very kind .
- You can stay as long as you like .
Give the locals something to talk about , eh ?
- No .
I 'm gonna go home .
I got what I came for .
I guess there 's not much more I can do .
- I 'll take you to the bus stop in the morning then .
- Well , I guess I 'll try to get some sleep .
- Good night , Carl .
- Good night , Sarah .
- He must have found water someplace else .
Well ...
we 've got plenty of time .
- Dicko , you can 't just go around killing
people cause you don 't like ' em .
- Why not , I haven 't killed anybody .
It 's the razorback , eh ?
Besides , the old coot 's been shooting his mouth off .
I 'm gonna have to teach him a lesson .
- Well , I don 't want no part of it .
- Yeah , but you never want to do anything fun .
One fart and you 're a hamburger .
Come on !
Get down !
Get down on the ground !
Come on !
I want to make sure you don 't go to the cops .
- What are you talking about , cops ?
- Why didn 't you stay in the truck ?
What did you do that for ?
Because he was gonna go you , you mug .
- He wasn 't gonna go me .
Pig 's arse .
You just spoilt everything .
- Spoilt what ?
- How 's he gonna feel it now ?
When we bust his legs .
- He 'll feel it soon enough won 't he .
Not if the razorback eats him before he wakes up .
- Jeez Dicko , you give me the shits sometimes .
If you 're gonna do it , just bloody do it .
- Sarah .
Get Sarah for me .
Go on . Run .
- Thank you .
You know , for the clothes and everything . - That 's alright .
Good luck .
- Good luck to you .
Off to New York .
I 've never even been to Sydney , you know .
- You will .
- I hope so .
Bye-bye .
- Bye .
- Ease on down , ease on down the road .
Traffic , eh ?
- Ease on down .
What did you do that for ?
- I don 't know .
- Weird .
- Come with me .
Jake !
- Sarah .
Sarah , wait a minute .
Sarah !
Where are you going ?
- I 'm gonna kill it , I know where it is !
- Jake couldn 't stop it .
What chance do we have ?
- We 'll get people together .
We 'll get it this time .
Follow me in Jake 's ute !
Benny !
Dicko !
- Hang about , Bill , you 're supposed to put your brakes on .
- My name 's Carl Winters .
As in Beth Winters .
- That 's no reason to .
- What did you do to my wife Benny ?
What did you do to my wife ?
- It was Dicko !
I wasn 't even there !
See , Dicko .
He 'd gone out and he 'd been drinking all day .
He 'd got a skinful and he 's off his brain .
Let me out !
- He was just gonna frighten her and it got out of hand ?
- Yeah .
And then this razorback came .
I 've never seen anything like it in my life before .
- Even though you weren 't there ?
Even though you weren 't there ?
You left my wife to the razorback ?
- I tried to help her .
- Just like you tried to help Jake Cullen .
Is that right ?
- I 'm not a violent man .
- Where 's your brother now ?
- I don 't know .
- Where 's your brother now Benny ?
- I don 't - -
- Where is your brother now ?
- Petpak !
He 's at Petpak !
Help me out , mate .
Don 't leave me here !
I 'll come and give you a hand !
Hey , mister , oi !
Don 't leave me , hey !
- Got it .
- Come on !
- Oh , shit !
Follow my car !
- Now !
- Stupid bloody woman .
- My dog 's bigger than that .
- Waste of bloody time .
- Bloody big razorback that , love .
Back to the pub , boys .
- Hey , Wallace !
You better put some light around the cess pool .
Otherwise the joint will be full of boars tonight , eh ?
Put ten out .
Gardner ?
Are you coming ?
Wallace ?
Sorry .
Would you like a hand ?
I 'm a kangaroo .
You 've got a really good sense of humour for a Septic .
- Well , shoot me !
Come on , man , shoot me !
You finished the kangaroo off !
Shoot me !
Wow !
- I 've got him on the screen , it was a second transmitter !
- Come on , love , it 's been a long day .
- He 's definitely at Petpak , he might even be inside .
If we can get out there quickly - -
- If he 's a Petpak , he won 't be molesting anyone .
- Is Carl there ?
- Who , over ?
- The American .
- I haven 't seen anyone .
- I 've got to go .
Over and out .
- Oh , God !
- Carl ?
Carl ?
- Sarah !
Oh , Jesus , no .
Sarah !
Get out of here !
It 's down there !
Get the hell out of here !
Get out !
- Oh , my God !
Oh , my God !
Come on !
This way !
Come on , come on !
Come on , you son of a bitch !
Sarah !
Come on .
Come on !
Come on , you scumbag !
You want me ?
Don 't just stand there .
I dare you .
You 're stupid and you stink too .
You think I 'm coming down there ?
You can kiss my ass .
Come on , you bastard .
Come on !